membershiptoolkit.com 2018-10-21

# Privacy Policy

**Updated: March 15, 2013**

At Membership Toolkit, Inc., we are dedicated to protecting your privacy and safeguarding your personally identifiable information. Our mission is to consistently exceed our customer's expectations. We are committed to adhering to the principles of applicable data protection and privacy laws throughout the United States. Amendments to this statement will be posted to this URL and will be effective when posted.

Personal information is information about an identifiable individual. Publicly available information, such as a public directory listing of your name, address, telephone number, or electronic address, is not considered to be personal information.

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on the Membership Toolkit website. When you use the Membership Toolkit Service we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie". We do not use cookies to spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy. They cannot invade your hard drive and steal information, and they cannot carry any executable code or viruses that could otherwise harm your computer.

We use cookies to help you navigate the Membership Toolkit website and Service as easily as possible, and to remember information about your current session. You must enable cookies on your web browser to use the Membership Toolkit Service.

**Security and Storage**

The Membership Toolkit website and Service has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your information. These safeguards include encryption of your data in transmission (using SSL or similar technologies).

We host our system in world-class datacenters with 24-hour security, redundancy, power, all the bells and whistles. We perform periodic backups of your data (in many cases multiple times per day), and maintain offsite storage of the data for a period of time, transmitted and stored in a secure fashion, to protect against data loss. During the process of development and troubleshooting the Membership Toolkit system, it may be necessary for us to look at pieces of your data to improve the service or resolve a problem, but your data is never shared with anyone outside of Membership Toolkit.

Additionally, you retain all rights of ownership to the data you have stored on the Membership Toolkit Service. We will not sell or share this data with any third parties. Your privacy and the privacy of your clients are of the utmost importance to us.

**Corrections and Updates**

You may keep your registration information current by visiting the account area of our Site. If you wish to change or update any of your personal information and are unable to do so, please contact us at [support@membershiptoolkit.com](mailto:support@membershiptoolkit.com).

**Questions**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or your dealings with the Membership Toolkit Site or Service, you can always contact us at [support@membershiptoolkit.com](mailto:support@membershiptoolkit.com).
